Guide to the Records of the Student Senators Council RG.44.0.1
New York University Archives
- Series III: Agendas & Minutes, 1975-2016; 13.48 Linear Feet in 29 manuscript boxes and 1 shared cassette box
  - Onassis Center, 1986-1987 (Box 34, Folder 6)
  - Organization & Governance (SCOG), 1986-1987 (Box 34, Folder 7)
  - Orientation Program, 1986-1987 (Box 34, Folder 8)
  - Report from the Chairman, 1986-1987 (Box 34, Folder 9)
  - Satellite Time, 1986-1987 (Box 34, Folder 10)
  - Staff Union, 1986-1987 (Box 34, Folder 11)
  - Student Credit Union, 1986-1987 (Box 34, Folder 12)
  - Student Escort Services, 1986-1987 (Box 34, Folder 13)
  - Washington Square News, 1986-1987 (Box 34, Folder 14)
  - Washington Square Park, 1986-1987 (Box 34, Folder 15)
  - World War 3 Theatre Group, 1986-1987 (Box 34, Folder 16)
  - Yearbook, 1986-1987 (Box 34, Folder 17)
  - Agendas & Minutes (UCSL only), 1987-1989 (Box 34, Folder 18-19)
  - Alumni Relations, 1987-1988 (Box 35, Folder 1)
  - Community Resource Initiative (CRI), 1987-1988 (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - Coors Beer Promotion, 1987-1988 (Box 35, Folder 3)
  - Resolutions, 1987-1988 (Box 35, Folder 4)
  - Rules - Governance Structures, 1987-1988 (Box 35, Folder 5)
  - Student Services, 1987-1988 (Box 35, Folder 6)
  - Tisch School Of The Arts (TSOA), 1987-1988 (Box 35, Folder 7)
  - Union (Staff) Local 3882, 1987-1988 (Box 35, Folder 8)
  - Minutes, 1988 (Box 35, Folder 9)
  - Academic Calendar, 1988-1989 (Box 35, Folder 10)
  - Agendas & Minutes (SSC only), 1988-1989 (Box 35, Folder 11)
  - Agendas & Minutes (UCSL only), 1988-1989 (Box 35, Folder 12-14)
  - Alternate Senators, 1988-1989 (Box 36, Folder 1)
  - Barney Building Protest, 1988-1989 (Box 36, Folder 2)
  - Broadway Show Ticket Sales, 1988-1989 (Box 36, Folder 3)
  - Calendar (Academic), 1988-1989 (Box 36, Folder 4)
  - Chancellor's Study Groups, 1988-1989 (Box 36, Folder 5)
  - Condolence Letters, 1988-1989 (Box 36, Folder 6)
  - Election of Officers, 1988-1989 (Box 36, Folder 7)
  - Faculty Council Minutes, 1988-1989 (Box 36, Folder 8)
  - Health Services, 1988-1989 (Box 36, Folder 9)
  - NYU Community Fund, 1988-1989 (Box 36, Folder 10)
  - Rules of Procedure, 1988-1989 (Box 36, Folder 11)
  - Security, 1988-1989 (Box 36, Folder 12)
  - Student/Faculty Relations, 1988-1989 (Box 36, Folder 13)
  - Student Government Handbook, 1988-1989 (Box 36, Folder 14)
  - Transportation Services, 1988-1989 (Box 36, Folder 15)
  - Vending Machines, 1988-1989 (Box 36, Folder 16)
  - Remarks: Vice President, 1988-1989 (Box 36, Folder 17)
  - Washington Square Park, 1988-1989 (Box 36, Folder 18)
  - Council Reports, 1989 (Box 36, Folder 19)
  - Advisement, 1989-1990 (Box 36, Folder 20)
  - Agendas & Minutes (SSC only), 1989-1990 (Box 36, Folder 21)
  - Agendas & Minutes (UCSL only), 1989-1990 (Box 36, Folder 22-23)
  - Book Exchange, 1989-1990 (Box 36, Folder 24)
  - Chancellor's Study Groups, 1989-1990 (Box 36, Folder 25)
  - Crisis & Information Hotline, 1989-1990 (Box 36, Folder 26)
  - Distinguished Teaching Award, 1989-1990 (Box 36, Folder 27)
  - Election of Officers, 1989-1990 (Box 36, Folder 28)
  - General Studies Program (GSP), 1989-1990 (Box 37, Folder 1)
  - Resolutions, 1989-1990 (Box 37, Folder 2)
  - School of Education, Health, Nursing, and Arts Professions (SEHNAP), 1989-1990 (Box 37, Folder 3)
  - Student Senators Council Agendas & Minutes, 1989-1990 (Box 37, Folder 4)
  - Tisch School Of The Arts (TSOA), 1989-1990 (Box 37, Folder 5)
  - Admissions Standards, 1990-1991 (Box 37, Folder 6)
  - Agendas & Minutes (SSC only), 1990-1991 (Box 37, Folder 7-8)
  - Agendas & Minutes (UCSL only), 1990-1991 (Box 37, Folder 9-11)
  - Construction - Space on Campus, 1990-1991 (Box 38, Folder 1)
  - Council Reports, 1990-1991 (Box 38, Folder 2)
  - Cross-School Registration, 1990-1991 (Box 38, Folder 3)
  - Gallatin Division, 1990-1991 (Box 38, Folder 4)
  - Graduate Affairs, 1990-1991 (Box 38, Folder 5)
  - Housing, 1990-1991 (Box 38, Folder 6)
  - Resolutions, 1990-1991 (Box 38, Folder 7)
  - Security, 1990-1991 (Box 38, Folder 8)
  - Agendas & Minutes (SSC only), 1991-1992 (Box 38, Folder 9-10)
  - Agendas & Minutes (UCSL only), 1991-1992 (Box 38, Folder 11-12)
  - Housing, 1991-1992 (Box 38, Folder 13)
  - Orgainzation & Governance (SCOG), 1991-1992 (Box 38, Folder 14)
  - Agendas & Minutes (UCSL only), 1992-1993 (Box 38, Folder 15-16)
  - Meetings with the President, 1992-1993 (Box 39, Folder 1)
  - Weekend Summits: Leadership Diversity, 1992-1993 (Box 39, Folder 2-3)
  - Agendas & Minutes, 1993-1994 (Box 39, Folder 4-6)
  - Agendas & Minutes (SSC only), 1993-1994 (Box 39, Folder 7, Box 40, Folder 1)
  - Agendas & Minutes (SSC only), 1994-1995 (Box 40, Folder 2-3)
  - Agendas & Minutes (UCSL only), 1994-1995 (Box 40, Folder 4-6)
  - Agendas & Minutes (SSC only), 1995-1996 (Box 41, Folder 1-2)
  - Agendas & Minutes (UCSL only), 1995-1996 (Box 41, Folder 3-5)
  - Academic Support Services, 1996-1997 (Box 42, Folder 1)
  - Agendas & Minutes, 1996-1997 (Box 42, Folder 2-3)
  - Agendas & Minutes (UCSL only), 1996-1997 (Box 42, Folder 4-5)
  - Agendas & Minutes (SSC only), 1997-1998 (Box 42, Folder 6)
  - Agendas & Minutes (UCSL only), 1997-1998 (Box 43, Folder 1-2)
  - Agendas & Minutes (SSC only), 1998-1999 (Box 43, Folder 3-4)
  - Agendas & Minutes (UCSL only), 1998-1999 (Box 43, Folder 5, Box 44, Folder 1)
  - Equal Commission, 1998-1999 (Box 44, Folder 2)
  - Village Improvement Planning VIP, 1998-1999 (Box 44, Folder Unknown)
  - Agendas & Minutes (SSC only), 1999-2000 (Box 44, Folder 4-5)
  - Agendas & Minutes (UCSL only), 1999-2000 (Box 44, Folder 6-7)
  - External Affairs/Albany Day, 1999-2000 (Box 44, Folder 8)
  - Agendas & Minutes (SSC only), 2000-2001 (Box 45, Folder 1)
  - Agendas & Minutes (UCSL only), 2000-2001 (Box 45, Folder 2-4)
  - Computers (NYU Net, Internet), 2000-2001 (Box 45, Folder 5)
  - Open Meetings, 2000-2001 (Box 45, Folder 6)
  - Agendas & Minutes (SSC only), 2001-2002 (Box 46, Folder 1)
  - Agendas & Minutes (UCSL only), 2001-2002 (Box 46, Folder 2-3)
  - Divides SSC & UCSL Full Mailings, 2002 (Box 46, Folder 4)
  - Agendas & Minutes (SSC only), 2002-2003 (Box 46, Folder 5)
  - Agendas & Minutes (UCSL only), 2002-2003 (Box 47, Folder 1-2)
  - Full Mailings for Meetings: SSC, 2002-2003 (Box 47, Folder 3)
  - Full Mailings for Meetings: UCSL, 2002-2003 (Box 47, Folder 4)
  - Student Services, 2002-2003 (Box 47, Folder 5)
  - Agendas & Minutes (SSC only), 2003-2004 (Box 47, Folder 6)
  - Agendas & Minutes (UCSL only), 2003-2004 (Box 48, Folder 1-3)
  - Full Mailings for Meetings: SSC, 2003-2004 (Box 48, Folder 4)
  - Full Mailings for Meetings: UCSL, 2003-2004 (Box 48, Folder 5)
  - Solomen Amendment, 2003-2004 (Box 48, Folder 6)
  - Agendas & Minutes, 2004-2008 (Box 49, Folder 5)
  - Agendas & Minutes (SSC only), 2004-2005 (Box 48, Folder 7)
  - Agendas & Minutes (UCSL only), 2004-2005 (Box 49, Folder 1-2)
  - Full Mailings for Meetings: SSC, 2004-2005 (Box 49, Folder 3)
  - Full Mailings for Meetings: UCSL, 2004-2005 (Box 49, Folder 4)
  - Agendas & Minutes (SSC only), 2005-2006 (Box 49, Folder 6)
  - Agendas & Minutes (UCSL only), 2005-2006 (Box 49, Folder 7, Box 50, Folder 1)
  - Commuter Students, 2005-2006 (Box 50, Folder 2)
  - Full Mailings for Meetings: SSC, 2005-2006 (Box 50, Folder 3)
  - Full Mailings for Meetings: UCSL, 2005-2006 (Box 50, Folder 4)
  - Kimmel Center, 2005-2006 (Box 50, Folder 5)
  - Student/Faculty Relations, 2005-2006 (Box 50, Folder 6)
  - Student Services, 2005-2006 (Box 50, Folder 7)
  - Agendas & Minutes (SSC only), 2006-2007 (Box 50, Folder 8)
  - Agendas & Minutes (UCSL only), 2006-2007 (Box 50, Folder 9)
  - Full Mailings for Meetings: SSC, 2006-2007 (Box 50, Folder 10)
  - Full Mailings for Meetings: UCSL, 2006-2007 (Box 50, Folder 11)
  - Minutes (SSC), 2006-2007 (Box 50, Folder 12, Box 51, Folder 1)
  - Agendas & Minutes (SSC only), 2007-2008
  - Agendas & Minutes (UCSL only), 2007-2008
  - Full Mailings for Meetings: SSC, 2007-2008
  - Full Mailings for Meetings: UCSL, 2007-2008
  - Agendas & Minutes (SSC only), 2008-2009 (Box 52, Folder 1)
  - Agendas & Minutes (UCSL only), 2008-2009 (Box 52, Folder 2-3)
  - Full Mailings for Meetings: SSC, 2008-2009 (Box 52, Folder 4)
  - Full Mailings for Meetings: UCSL, 2008-2009 (Box 52, Folder 5)
  - Minutes & Agendas, 2011-2012 (Box 52, Folder 6)
  - Agendas, 2012 (Box 52, Folder 7)
  - Agenda & Minutes (UCSL), 2012-2013 (Box 53, Folder 1)
  - Agenda (UCSL), 2013 (Box 53, Folder 2)
  - University Committee on Student Life Agenda, 2013 (Box 53, Folder 3)
  - Choir Circle Meeting Agendas, 2013-2014 (Box 53, Folder 4)
  - Past - Agenda, 2013-2014 (Box 53, Folder 5)
  - Senate Agenda, 2013-2014 (Box 53, Folder 6)
  - 2015 Elections Agenda, 2016 (Box 53, Folder 7)
- Series IV: Memos and Reports, 1976-2014; 14.88 Linear Feet in 34 manuscript boxes
  Series IV contains memos and reports circulated within the Student Senators Council. Some memos addressed to administrators are also contained in this series. The memos and reports are used to update members and administrators on topics discussed at the monthly SSC meetings.
  - Memorandum - Reviews and Other Committees, 1976 (Box 53, Folder 8)
  - Report on Independent Student Coalition, 1976-1977 (Box 53, Folder 9)
  - Student Life - Bill Dunlap, 1976-1977 (Box 53, Folder 10)
  - 4x4 Calendar - Back Up Materials and Current Business, 1977-1978 (Box 53, Folder 11)
  - The Courier, 1977-1978 (Box 53, Folder 12)
  - Dean Rochell on Bobst Library, 1977-1978 (Box 53, Folder 13)
  - Great Teacher Award, 1977-1978 (Box 53, Folder 14)
  - Master Charge, 1977-1978 (Box 54, Folder 1)
  - Memos to Administrators, 1977-1978 (Box 54, Folder 2)
  - Memos to Members (SSC), 1977-1978 (Box 53, Folder 15)
  - Memos to Members (UCSL), 1977-1978 (Box 53, Folder 16)
  - Student Health Insurance, 1977-1978 (Box 54, Folder 3)
  - Student Leadership Training Workshop, 1977-1978 (Box 54, Folder 4)
  - University Without Walls Danner Case, 1977-1978 (Box 54, Folder 5)
  - Committee on Evening Students, 1978-1979 (Box 54, Folder 6)
  - New York Public Interest Research Group (NYPIRG), 1978-1979 (Box 54, Folder 7)
  - Reports on the Libraries, 1978-1979 (Box 54, Folder 8)
  - Student Senates Council - Memos to Members, 1978-1979 (Box 54, Folder 9)
  - University Committee on Student Life - Memos to Members, 1978-1979 (Box 54, Folder 10)
  - Year of the Child, 1978-1979 (Box 54, Folder 11)
  - Meeting Memos and Reports, 1979 (Box 54, Folder 12)
  - Affirmative Action, 1979-1980 (Box 54, Folder 13)
  - Courier, 1979-1980 (Box 54, Folder 14)
  - Faculty Retirement, 1979-1980 (Box 54, Folder 15)
  - Faculty/Student Relations (Task Force), 1979-1980 (Box 54, Folder 16)
  - Judson Hall: Funding, 1979-1980 (Box 54, Folder 17)
  - Long Range Planning, 1979-1980 (Box 54, Folder 18)
  - Luncheon with Bennett, 1979-1980 (Box 54, Folder 19)
  - Memos to Administrators, 1979-1980 (Box 54, Folder 20)
  - Memos to Members, 1979-1980 (Box 54, Folder 21)
  - New York Public Interest Research Group (NYPIRG), 1979-1980 (Box 55, Folder 1)
  - Sexual Harrassment, 1979-1980 (Box 55, Folder 2)
  - Student Bar Association: Law School, 1979-1980 (Box 55, Folder 3)
  - Washington Square News, 1979-1980 (Box 55, Folder 4)
  - West 3rd Street Theater, 1979-1980 (Box 55, Folder 5)
  - 4x4 Calendar, 1980-1981 (Box 55, Folder 6)
  - Calendar Information 1969-1978, 1980-1981 (Box 55, Folder 7)
  - Commencement, 1980-1981 (Box 55, Folder 8)
  - Memos to Administrators, 1980-1981 (Box 55, Folder 9)
  - Memos to Members, 1980-1981 (Box 55, Folder 10)
  - The New Torch: Status, 1980-1981 (Box 55, Folder 11)
  - New York Public Interest Research Group (NYPIRG), 1980-1981 (Box 55, Folder 12)
  - New York State Assembly Intern Program, 1980-1981 (Box 55, Folder 13)
  - Professor in Residence Brittany, 1980-1981 (Box 55, Folder 14)
  - School Councils, 1980-1981 (Box 55, Folder 15)
  - Humanities Council Seminars, 1981-1982 (Box 55, Folder 16)
  - Meetings of the Committee Conveners, 1981-1982 (Box 55, Folder 17)
  - Meeting with the President, 1981-1982 (Box 55, Folder 18)
  - Memos to Administrators, 1981-1982 (Box 55, Folder 19, Box 56, Folder 1)
  - Memos to Members, 1981-1982 (Box 56, Folder 2)
  - Mid Year Reports, 1981-1982 (Box 56, Folder 3)
  - New York Public Interest Research Group (NYPIRG), 1981-1982 (Box 56, Folder 4)
  - New York State Assembly Intern Program, 1981-1982 (Box 56, Folder 5)
  - Presidential Inauguration, 1981-1982 (Box 56, Folder 6)
  - Security, 1981-1982 (Box 56, Folder 7)
  - Student Affairs, 1981-1982 (Box 56, Folder 8)
  - Student Senators Council - Memos to Members, 1981-1982 (Box 56, Folder 9)
  - Senate House Advisory Review Board, 1981-1982 (Box 56, Folder 10-11)
  - Student Services, 1981-1982 (Box 57, Folder 1)
  - Survey, 1981-1982 (Box 57, Folder 2)
  - Termination of Programs Rights, 1981-1982 (Box 57, Folder 3)
  - The Torch, 1981-1982 (Box 57, Folder 4)
  - Town Meeting, 1981-1982 (Box 57, Folder 5)
  - UCSL Newsletter, 1981-1982 (Box 57, Folder 6)
  - USA-NYU Collective Bargaining, 1981-1982 (Box 57, Folder 7)
  - Use of Facilities, 1981-1982 (Box 57, Folder 8)
  - Volunteer/Community Relations, 1981-1982 (Box 57, Folder 9)
  - Washington Square News, 1981-1982 (Box 57, Folder 10)
  - Widman on Marcus, 1981-1982 (Box 57, Folder 11)
  - Report of the Committee on Sexual Assault and Personal Safety, 1982 (Box 57, Folder 12)
  - Calendar for the Year, 1982-1983 (Box 57, Folder 13)
  - Deans Review Process, 1982-1983 (Box 57, Folder 14)
  - Election Guidelines, 1982-1983 (Box 57, Folder 15)
  - Election of Officers, 1982-1983 (Box 57, Folder 16)
  - Government Aid to Higher Education, 1982-1983 (Box 57, Folder 17)
  - Improved Communications with Administration, 1982-1983 (Box 57, Folder 18)
  - Meetings of the Committee Conveners, 1982-1983 (Box 57, Folder 19)
  - Memos to Administrators, 1982-1983 (Box 57, Folder 20)
  - Memos to Members (SSC), 1982-1983 (Box 57, Folder 21)
  - Memos to Members (UCSL), 1982-1983 (Box 57, Folder 22)
  - Termination of Programs Rights, 1982-1983 (Box 57, Folder 23)
  - Security, 1982-1983 (Box 57, Folder 24)
  - Solomon Amendment: Draft/Aid, 1982-1983 (Box 57, Folder 25)
  - Student Councils, 1982-1983 (Box 57, Folder 26)
  - Student Services, 1982-1983 (Box 57, Folder 27)
  - Student Survey, 1982-1983 (Box 57, Folder 28)
  - Systems Analyst, 1982-1983 (Box 58, Folder 1)
  - Confidentiality, 1983 (Box 58, Folder 2)
  - Great Teachers Awards, 1983 (Box 58, Folder 3)
  - Miracle at Washington Square, 1983 (Box 58, Folder 4)
  - Newsletters, 1983 (Box 58, Folder 5)
  - NYU Community Fund, 1983 (Box 58, Folder 6)
  - Secretary of the University Senate, 1983 (Box 58, Folder 7)
  - Calendar for the Year, 1983-1984 (Box 58, Folder 8)
  - Committee Assignments, 1983-1984 (Box 58, Folder 9)
  - Committee Description: UCSL, 1983-1984 (Box 58, Folder 10)
  - Committee Spokespersons, 1983-1984 (Box 58, Folder 11)
  - Fundraising: First Year Report, 1983-1984 (Box 58, Folder 12)
  - Government Education Policies, 1983-1984 (Box 58, Folder 13)
  - Memos to Members, 1983-1984 (Box 58, Folder 14)
  - Orientation, 1983-1984 (Box 58, Folder 15)
  - Program Board, 1983-1984 (Box 58, Folder 16)
  - School Student Council, 1983-1984 (Box 58, Folder 17)
  - Student Affairs Organizational Chart, 1983-1984 (Box 58, Folder 18)
  - Health Center Survery & Report, 1984 (Box 58, Folder 19)
  - Public Affairs, 1984 (Box 58, Folder 20)
  - Student Information System (SIS), 1984 (Box 58, Folder 21)
  - Calendar for the Year, 1984-1985 (Box 58, Folder 22)
  - Coles Recreation Center Advisory Board, 1984-1985 (Box 58, Folder 23)
  - Council Contingency Funds (CCF), 1984-1985 (Box 58, Folder 24)
  - Exit Interview Schedule, 1984-1985 (Box 58, Folder 25)
  - Housing, 1984-1985 (Box 58, Folder 26)
  - Housing Reports, 1984-1985 (Box 59, Folder 11)
  - Issues Pending, 1984-1985 (Box 59, Folder 1)
  - Memos to & from Administrators, 1984-1985 (Box 59, Folder 2)
  - Memos to Members (SSC), 1984-1985 (Box 59, Folder 3)
  - Memos to Members (UCSL), 1984-1985 (Box 59, Folder 4)
  - Newsletter, 1984-1985 (Box 59, Folder 5)
  - Ombudsman, 1984-1985 (Box 59, Folder 6)
  - Physical Examination Fee - School of Education, Health, Nursing, and Arts Professions (SEHNAP), 1984-1985 (Box 59, Folder 7)
  - South Africa (Apartheid), 1984-1985 (Box 59, Folder 8)
  - Student/Faculty Relations, 1984-1985 (Box 59, Folder 9)
  - University Ombudsman, 1984-1985 (Box 59, Folder 10)
  - Faculty & Staff Overview of the NYU Telephone Project, 1985 (Box 59, Folder 12)
  - Agendas & Minutes - Memos (SSC only), 1985-1986 (Box 59, Folder 13-14)
  - Equity, 1985-1986 (Box 60, Folder 1)
  - Memos to & from Administrators, 1985-1986 (Box 60, Folder 2)
  - Memos to & from Members, 1985-1986 (Box 60, Folder 3)
  - South Africa, 1985-1986 (Box 60, Folder 4)
  - Student/Faculty Relations, 1985-1986 (Box 60, Folder 5)
  - Student Guide to NYU, 1985-1986 (Box 60, Folder 6)
  - Student Lounge: Bobst, 1985-1986 (Box 60, Folder 7)
  - Animal Experimentation/Abuse, 1986-1987 (Box 60, Folder 8)
  - Health Services, 1986-1987 (Box 60, Folder 9)
  - Leadership Workshop/Weekend, 1986-1987 (Box 60, Folder 10)
  - Memos to & from Administrators, 1986-1987 (Box 60, Folder 11-12)
  - Memos to & from Members, 1986-1987 (Box 60, Folder 13)
  - NYU Anti-Discrimination Policy, 1986-1987 (Box 61, Folder 1)
  - Student Government at NYU, 1986-1987 (Box 61, Folder 2)
  - Student's Guide to NYU, 1986-1987 (Box 61, Folder 3)
  - Student Services, 1986-1987 (Box 61, Folder 4)
  - Deep Focus Budgetary Appeal Report, 1987 (Box 61, Folder 5)
  - Cohesive Community Study Group, 1987-1988 (Box 61, Folder 6)
  - Day Care Center, 1987-1988 (Box 61, Folder 7)
  - Memos to & from Administrators, 1987-1988 (Box 61, Folder 8)
  - Religious Holidays: Calendar, 1987-1988 (Box 61, Folder 9)
  - Student/Faculty Relations, 1987-1988 (Box 61, Folder 10)
  - New York University Long Range Plan - Interim Report of the University-Wide Planning Commission, Summary Report of the Schools and Colleges, 1988 (Box 61, Folder 11, Box 62, Folder 1)
  - Proposed Resolution to Reaffirm the University Calendar Policy on Religious Holidays, 1988 (Box 62, Folder 2)
  - Archives, 1988-1989 (Box 62, Folder 3)
  - Calendar of the Year (Meetings), 1988-1989 (Box 62, Folder 4)
  - Childcare, 1988-1989 (Box 62, Folder 5-6)
  - General Studies Program (SCE), 1988-1989 (Box 62, Folder 7)
  - Memos to & from Administrators, 1988-1989 (Box 62, Folder 8)
  - Samples to Start (FC/SSC), 1989-1990, 1988-1989 (Box 62, Folder 9-10)
  - Samples to Start (SSC), 1989-1990, 1988-1989 (Box 63, Folder 1-2)
  - Senate, 1988-1989 (Box 63, Folder 3)
  - Student Insurance Program, 1988-1989 (Box 63, Folder 4)
  - Crisis Hotline, 1989 (Box 63, Folder 5)
  - Report of the Senate Commission on the Use and Abuse of Alcohol and Other Drug Among Students, 1989 (Box 63, Folder 6)
  - Alcohol: Report on Use & Abuse, 1989-1990 (Box 63, Folder 7)
  - Calendar of Meetings, SSC & UCSL versions, 1989-1990 (Box 63, Folder 8)
  - Childcare, 1989-1990 (Box 63, Folder 9)
  - Memos to & from Administrators, 1989-1990 (Box 64, Folder 1)
  - Program Board, 1989-1990 (Box 64, Folder 2)
  - Registration/Mop-Up, 1989-1990 (Box 64, Folder 3)
  - Sample Packets for Sept & Blanks, 1989-1990 (Box 64, Folder 4)
  - School Student Council Reports, 1989-1990 (Box 64, Folder 5)
  - Search Committee: VP for Student Affairs, 1989-1990 (Box 64, Folder 6)
  - Special Interest Housing, 1989-1990 (Box 64, Folder 7)
  - Student/Faculty Relations, 1989-1990 (Box 64, Folder 8)
  - Washington Square News, 1989-1990 (Box 64, Folder 9)
  - Memorandum, 1990 (Box 64, Folder 10)
  - African-American, Hispanic, Asian, and Native American (AHANA) Senators-at-Large Proposal, 1990-1991 (Box 64, Folder 11)
  - Committee Meeting, 1990-1991 (Box 64, Folder 12)
  - Elections, 1990-1991 (Box 64, Folder 13)
  - Memos to & from Administrators, 1990-1991 (Box 64, Folder 14-15)
  - NYU Presidency, 1990-1991 (Box 64, Folder 16)
  - Sexual Assault, 1990-1991 (Box 64, Folder 17)
  - Student/Faculty Relations, 1990-1991 (Box 64, Folder 18)
  - Student Life, Office of (Memos), 1990-1991 (Box 65, Folder 1)
  - Student Services, 1990-1991 (Box 65, Folder 2)
  - Washington Square News, 1990-1991 (Box 65, Folder 3)
  - Accident in Washington Square Park (4/23), 1991-1992 (Box 65, Folder 4)
  - Alumni/Student Relations, 1991-1992 (Box 65, Folder 5)
  - Calendar of Meetings (SSC & UCSL versions), 1991-1992 (Box 65, Folder 6)
  - General Studies Program (SCE), 1991-1992 (Box 65, Folder 7)
  - Protest and Dissent, Guidelines, 1991-1992 (Box 65, Folder 8)
  - Resolutions, 1991-1992 (Box 65, Folder 9)
  - Sexual Assault (Statement on Sexual Harrassment), 1991-1992 (Box 65, Folder 10)
  - Space, 1991-1992 (Box 65, Folder 11)
  - Student/Faculty Relations, 1991-1992 (Box 65, Folder 12)
  - Student Services, 1991-1992 (Box 65, Folder 13)
  - Tutoring, University-Wide, 1991-1992 (Box 65, Folder 14)
  - Washington Square News, 1991-1992 (Box 65, Folder 15)
  - Memos from President, 1992 (Box 66, Folder 1)
  - Memos to SSC, 1992 (Box 66, Folder 2)
  - All-University Yearbook, 1992-1993 (Box 66, Folder 3)
  - CARP, 1992-1993 (Box 66, Folder 4)
  - Childcare, 1992-1993 (Box 66, Folder 5)
  - Commencement, 1992-1993 (Box 66, Folder 6)
  - Embezzlement, 1992-1993 (Box 66, Folder 7)
  - Faculty/Student Relations: Olivia, 1992-1993 (Box 66, Folder 8)
  - Koppenaal Commission ("EQUAL"), 1992-1993 (Box 66, Folder 9)
  - Memos to & from Administrators, 1992-1993 (Box 66, Folder 10-11)
  - Newsletter, 1992-1993 (Box 67, Folder 1)
  - Purple Bible, 1992-1993 (Box 67, Folder 2)
  - Space, 1992-1993 (Box 67, Folder 3)
  - Village Improvement Planning (VIP), 1992-1993 (Box 67, Folder 4)
  - Washington Square News, 1992-1993 (Box 67, Folder 5)
  - Memorandum, 1993 (Box 67, Folder 6)
  - Village Improvement Plan, 1993 (Box 67, Folder 7)
  - Childcare, 1993-1994 (Box 67, Folder 8)
  - Equal Commission, 1993-1994 (Box 67, Folder 9)
  - Greek Issues, 1993-1994 (Box 67, Folder 10)
  - Memos to & from Administrators, 1993-1994 (Box 67, Folder 11-12)
  - Middle State Review, 1993-1994 (Box 67, Folder 13)
  - Photographic Chemical Recycling, 1993-1994 (Box 67, Folder 14)
  - Resolutions, 1993-1994 (Box 67, Folder 15)
  - Security, 1993-1994 (Box 67, Folder 16)
  - Space, 1993-1994 (Box 67, Folder 17)
  - Student/Faculty Relations, 1993-1994 (Box 67, Folder 18)
  - Washington Square News, 1993-1994 (Box 67, Folder 19)
  - Academic Support Services, 1994-1995 (Box 67, Folder 20)
  - Americorps, 1994-1995 (Box 67, Folder 21)
  - Computers (NYU Net, Internet), 1994-1995 (Box 67, Folder 22)
  - Equal Commission, 1994-1995 (Box 68, Folder 1)
  - External Affairs/Albany Day, 1994-1995 (Box 68, Folder 2)
  - Forum, 1994-1995 (Box 68, Folder 3)
  - General Studies Program (SCE), 1994-1995 (Box 68, Folder 4)
  - Information Sent to SSC/UCSL, 1994-1995 (Box 68, Folder 5)
  - Memorandum, 1994-1995 (Box 68, Folder 6)
  - Memos to and From Administrators, 1994-1995 (Box 252, Folder 2-3)
  - Middle State Review, 1994-1995 (Box 68, Folder 7)
  - Pending Issues, 1994-1995 (Box 68, Folder 8)
  - Newsletter, 1994-1995 (Box 68, Folder 9)
  - Rice Commission, 1994-1995 (Box 68, Folder 10)
  - Security, 1994-1995 (Box 68, Folder 11)
  - Space, 1994-1995 (Box 68, Folder 12)
  - Student Councils, 1994-1995 (Box 68, Folder 13)
  - Student Services (Food, Health), 1994-1995 (Box 68, Folder 14)
  - Washington Square News, 1994-1995 (Box 68, Folder 15)
  - Academic Affairs, 1995-1996 (Box 69, Folder 1)
  - Academic Issues (Ad Hoc), 1995-1996 (Box 69, Folder 2)
  - Academic Support Services, 1995-1996 (Box 69, Folder 3)
  - Childcare, 1995-1996 (Box 69, Folder 4)
  - Computers (NYU Net, Internet), 1995-1996 (Box 69, Folder 5)